Man, I'm wasting away over here.
After we visit my bro's grave, Dave,
what do you say we find a
place to get something to eat?
I'm good, but don't let me stop you.
Says here there's a new Italian
restaurant, and it's just up the road.
Wait, isn't that where the cemetery is?
Not the best place for a restaurant,
or anything for that matter.
Oh, Josuke,
this is just the kind of wacky food destination
that brings people in from all over.
It's to die for!
My mouth won't stop watering!
Or whatever it is the Fats
say, I just want to go.
Come on, Josuke, what do you say?
This is it?
I thought this building was vacant.
Maybe they remodeled it.
It sure has character.
Huh?
That's weird.
What's diner dependent mean?
I'm digging the vibe
this place has going on.
Benvenuto.
Two today?
Here, please feel free to have a seat.
Oh, don't mind if I do.
Here you go.
Uh, right.
So chef, you a foreigner or what?
Si, signore.
I am originally from Italy.
My name is Tonio Trendi,
but you can call me Tonio.
This is the best day ever!
I finally get to eat
authentic Italian food!
My role as a chef has
taken me to many countries.
I've used the flavors
of my homeland and fused
them with the best culinary
traditions in the world.
Now I've made my way to Japan
in search of new opportunities.
Your Mariah is such a magnificent town.
You can find several farms with
many kinds of fresh produce.
Its fruity de mari are great too.
I adore it here.
Using Morio's wonderful ingredients,
I plan to make you a meal that will tickle
the taste buds and delight your senses.
Well, all right then.
What do you think I should order?
Actually, I'll choose after
you show us the menu. Menu?
I'm sorry, but we don't use those. Huh?
What are you talking about?
What kind of restaurant doesn't use menus?
What I serve depends on
the patron I'm serving.
Well, you're serving
me, and I want the menu.
That won't do.
First, I have to examine the customer.
Then I decide what to prepare for them.
You've got to be kidding!
You don't let your customers choose
what they want to eat for themselves?
Alright.
Let's see now.
You had diarrhea yesterday.
Your intestinal walls are inflamed.
And it's obvious you're sleep deprived.
Yes, you only got four hours last night.
Which of course explains the puffy eyes.
Now let's see your left hand.
Your right foot is infected with a fungus.
You also have two cavities and
your left shoulder is stiff, yes?
What?
How the hell did you know all that?
Everything you said
was right on the money!
It's all in the hands, amigo mio.
They are like a window into your health.
Oh, please excuse me.
And what will you be having, signore?
Oh, I'm not all that hungry.
But I'll take a cup of
coffee if you have any.
Make it a cappuccino.
Ho Capt, signore.
This guy can talk up his fancy
dishes as much as he wants.
Healthy food tastes like dog shit.
If it's even a little disgusting,
we don't have to pay for it.
We can just complain and leave.
Roger.
Hey, Josuke, this water!
No wait, it has to be
mineral water. What about it?
I've never been as totally sure about
something as I am right this moment.
This is the best water
that I've ever tasted!
Amazing!
It's overflowing with sophistication!
It's like something a
mountain princess playing a
harp would drink as she
strums a beautiful melody!
It's wonderfully fresh and smooth!
Like the glorious first taste of water after
wandering in the desert for three days!
Wow! Yeah! You weren't
joking! It's amazing!
Divine!
You're right!
It's first-rate!
I wonder if they'll tell us
what brand of water it is?
You know,
this water's so good, I think I'm actually
going to shed a few tears over it.
Come on.
A little sip of water isn't worth
weeping over no matter how good it is.
It must be its purity.
Do you have a handkerchief on you?
The waterworks are in full force.
The tears just keep coming.
They won't stop.
Okuyasu, you're acting weird, man.
Are you okay?
What the? Okuyasu! Holy shit!
What the hell is going
on with these tears?
They just keep pouring out of me!
Hey! Okuyasu!
I don't want to freak you out even more,
but the white parts of your eyes
are getting all shriveled and loose!
Momento.
Please try to remain calm.
You bastard!
The hell did you give Okuyasu to drink?
Tranquilo, signore.
His eyes have only been
temporarily withered.
He had 50,000-year-old
mineral water made from
melted snow procured from
Mount Kilimanjaro in Africa.
It flushes the ice interior
of harmful contaminants and
is an effective treatment in
cases of sleep deprivation.
The reason you didn't cry
after drinking the water is
because you obtained an adequate
amount of sleep last night.
Josuke!
I'm not sleepy anymore!
To be perfectly honest with
you, I feel spectacular!
Like I slept a full ten hours!
Wait a second!
You can't be serious!
Are you telling me there's
nothing wrong with your eyes?
Exactly!
When you drink water this good, it's
only natural for the tears to flow.
Trust me, Josuke, it's
nothing to be worried about.
I cried way more than this
when I watched Champ on video.
Thanks for Karen, but I
feel like a billion yen!
Is that a fact?
You bet your ass it is.
Here's your cappuccino.
Oh, thanks.
So, shall we continue
with the next course?
Wow, looks grum-diddly-yumptious.
For our antipasto, I've prepared
insalata caprese with mozzarella.
Excuse me, but what's Masazo?
Goodness, you've never
heard of mozzarella before.
It's a soft, low-fat
cheese that's quite tasty.
It is a national favorite in Italy.
The first people to use tomatoes as a
culinary ingredient were the Italians.
The Italian people lead the entire world
when it comes to tomato based cuisine.
I'm not bragging.
It's the honest truth.
We take pride in our work
Now I hope you enjoy
your meal sir. Trust me.
I will
Well this dish is pretty
good I'll give you that I
dare say this is very good
but even so the cheese itself
doesn't leave much of an
impression which is a shame after
all the hype no no it's not
meant to be eaten by itself,
you have to add tomato to it. Say what?
Adding a tomato sounds weird.
Well, all right, but here in
Japan, we have sensitive palates.
This is gonna have to be
mind-blowing to pass the tasty test.
Um.
Oh my God!
It's incredible how the tomatoey nectar
gently caresses the fresh, delicate cheese.
What a great combination.
The cheese and tomato enrich each other.
It's a perfect symphony, I tell you.
A harmony of tantalizing flavors, A dynamic
duo the likes of Simon and Garfunkel!
or even Abbott and Costello.
It's like the writer-illustrator
team Osuo Takamori
and Tetsuya Chiba from the
comic Ashta no Joe! Crazy.
Nothing makes me happier than
knowing you enjoyed my cooking.
Hey, old buddy, old pal.
You think you can share some
of that with your bestie?
Not on your life.
You can order your own
as a salad, Konichi.
You're not getting any
of mine, you got that?
Even if you were starving to death,
I still wouldn't give you a
piece of this yummy goodness!
So good!
Everything I've been through has been
worth it to get beat at this moment!
Dick!
I knew you were a stingy son of a
bitch, but this takes it to a new level!
Alright, fine.
I will have the same thing he's having.
Pocopito.
That said,
the only one getting his
stiff shoulder corrected
today will be the gentleman
sitting to your left.
Huh?
Stiff shoulder?
But you know,
I am starting to get a little
bit hot under the collar,
and for some reason I'm all sweaty.
Signore, might I humbly
suggest you remove your jacket.
What the hell?
Why am I so itchy all of a sudden?
What's going on?
What's all this flaky stuff
sticking to my fingers?
Semplice.
It's dead skin. Dead skin!
This is proof that we've greatly improved
your metabolic function and circulation.
The calcium,
vitamins and minerals of the
antipasto have stimulated
your thyroid and its
metabolic hormone secretion.
The harmful cells are being
expelled as dead skin,
which is why you've been overcome
with an itching sensation.
Molto Bone, signore.
Keep scratching like that.
Because at the rate you're going, the
dead skin will be gone in no time.
Okuyasu!
Come on, man, you have to cut it out!
This dead skin's the size of a softball!
We're digging into your
shoulder's muscle now!
No!
You're wrong, Josuke!
I'm so limber!
My shoulder's crazy flexible now!
Wow, it's so springy and light,
it's almost like I'm floating!
Check it out, my shoulders have never been
supple enough to bend around like this!
It's almost like I don't
have any bones at all!
The stiffness I had is good and gone!
If you'll excuse me, I'll be
heading back to the kitchen.
That pasta isn't going to get up and
serve itself while we stand here and chat.
He's amazing!
Actually, he's incredible!
We should come here to eat more often!
I don't think so.
This is getting way too freaky.
There is something seriously
weird about this guy's cooking.
Now, shall we continue with the next dish?
This is the primo piatto.
Today is pasta.
Spaghetti alla puttanesca.
Known as horse pasta,
this dish supposedly originated with
prostitutes who favored its easy preparation.
While cheese is not usually added
to pasta prepared with garlic,
this dish is a notable exception.
This spaghetti, am I crazy or
does it have chili flakes in it?
An astute observation.
This special sauce used
in spaghetti puttanesca is
one of the oldest recipes
found in Italian cuisine.
And not to brag, but my hometown,
Napoli, is considered its birthplace.
So, of course, I give it the
highest possible recommendation.
You should have said that earlier.
I can't eat anything spicy.
The only kind of curry
rice I can handle is that
mild Vermont curry that
has apples and honey in it.
Oh, and don't get me started
on wasabi with sushi.
I can't do it! It's too spicy!
It's like eating fire!
There's a simple solution, then. Ready?
Don't eat it.
If it's not to your liking,
don't force yourself.
I'd be more than happy to
remove the pasta from your bill.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'll prepare the main course.
I hope the secondo piato
will suit you better.
But so you know, signore,
I make my spaghetti to
be enjoyed even by those
who have the lowest
tolerance for spicy foods.
So I can eat this even though it's spicy?
Hot!
I know Tonio's a master chef.
Anybody with taste buds would agree.
And if you ask me, I'd even
say the guy's a genius.
But this really wasn't his best work.
No, I think you lucked out
with your spice intolerance.
Huh?
Hasn't it crossed your mind that this food
and water might be a little too weird?
Something's shady.
What do you mean by shady?
Spicy?
You scratched off a
softball-sized wad of dead skin,
and that's after you
cried a freaking river.
I guess I did.
But that time I went to
Shirabu Onsen in Yamagata,
I lost even more dead
skin than I did today?
and my back got better.
It's totally normal, isn't it?
Hot!
Listen!
Remember what I said about that little
chat with Hazamada in the hospital?
I don't know why, but it
seems that stand users...
He said stand users are
inadvertently drawn to each other.
Josuke, are you really trying to
tell me Tonio's a stand user? Shh!
We can't say for sure yet, which is why
I chose the word shady. Got it. Shady.
Oh, come on!
Why is it so hot?
If you can't handle spicy food,
maybe you should quit trying to
stuff it in your mouth already.
You're right.
I should just give up on it.
Spicy food and meat don't
mix at all. That's true.
But for some reason, I can't stop
tasting this delicious sauce.
Why are you eating that?
Yeah, it's weird, right?
I wouldn't usually be able to
chow down on anything just spicy.
But now...
I can't stop!
After that first bite, the
spice bit back and won't let go!
It's like eating your weight
in beans during a festival.
And even though they don't taste good,
before you know it, you've eaten a whole bag!
And you don't regret a damn thing,
because all you can feel
is your body wanting more!
Hey, I told you to stop eating that crap!
I can't explain it, but
I'm getting even hungrier!
The more spaghetti I ate, the
more that I want to scarf down!
Tasty!
Okuyasu, calm down!
Holy shit! Your tooth!
That's the cavity I had!
The rotten tooth just fell out!
Actually, I think one of the
bottom teeth had a cavity, too. Ah!
I was right, another rotten tooth.
Whoa, a new molar is already growing in.
I've had enough of this.
Time to find out what that
chef from hell's planning.
Do it, Shining Diamond!
But I wasn't done with that!
Sorry to ruin the meal,
but I'm reverting the ingredients
back to their original forms!
Hey, what in the world were
those little things, Josuke?
It's a stand.
So my hunch was right after all.
Tony Otrendy's a stand user.
Okuyasu, are you okay?
My sleepiness is finally gone.
My stiffness melted away.
And my cavities were replaced.
But my stomach hurts.
I've never felt such
excruciating pain in my life!
Hang on! Tonio!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
Where is he?
So he's already finished our main course.
Excelente.
I want you to enjoy it.
Judging from this, it appears my main dish
of lamb with apple relish was a success.
Quiet!
What exactly do you think
you're doing back here?
Did you see?
Answer the question, per favore!
Did you enter my kitchen to spy on me?
Now prepare yourself, signore!
You're going to pay dearly!
Give me one good reason
why I should stand here and
listen to you hurl around
threats about making me pay!
I should threaten you!
Now, what the hell are you trying
to do with that food of yours?
Okuyasu, wait a sec,
what are you eating now?
I can't stand it, my stomach
hurts, but I can't stop eating.
A tangy sweet apple relish
combined with juice from
the lambs makes every
single morsel pure ecstasy.
Who knew food could taste
this finger licking good?
For the love of God, drop the meat.
This is the best day ever.
It's like a waterfall of
pleasure washing over me.
Amazing.
What?
My guts fell out!
My stomach's dying!
Uncle Yasu!
I'm putting an end to this!
Oh no!
Wash your disgusting hands
with softness instant!
Honestly, entering a kitchen
without permission is inexcusable!
Ascolti, cleanliness in the
kitchen is priority one, amico mio!
Wait, wash my hands?
You aren't trying to kill me?
Hey, Josuke!
It's like my insides
have been rejuvenated!
Not only that, I'm completely
full and feel as fit as a fiddle!
And best of all, my diarrhea
tummy's all better! What?
Oh my, that's wonderful to hear!
I love knowing that my cooking brought
happiness and health to a customer.
Believe me when I tell you,
there's no greater sense of joy and
accomplishment for me than
nurturing a hungry soul.
The puppy!
With such unconventional flavors,
I wanted him to taste testy.
Our furry friend here was having
a bit of a digestive problem, too.
So, you mean, you just wanted
Okuyasu to eat a good meal?
You don't have ulterior motives? Hmm?
What else could a chef want from a
patron but for them to enjoy the food?
The thought gets me out
of bed in the morning.
It's everything I could ever hope for.
And to be clear, you're a stand user.
We have them too.
Oh!
I can't believe my eyes!
Where to start?
A while back I was traveling the
world in search of the perfect cuisine
when out of the blue I discovered
I had these fantastical powers.
Never in my wildest dreams would I have
thought I'd meet others similar to myself.
Even so, that's no excuse!
You have to possess common sense!
You touched my kitchen without
washing your filthy hands!
If I was cross with you earlier,
it's because I'm aware that the
kitchen's worst enemy is germs!
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
That didn't even cross my mind.
I hope you're ready to put in some work.
Now, shall we continue the cookie?
Dessert is... pudding?
Ha!
I'm too manly for this stuff.
Well, I'll eat it, but it
doesn't mean I'm gonna like it.
I'll...
Oh, my God!
You really are a genius!
You are amazing!
A brilliant artist! Yeah, yeah.
Yuck it up, Okuyasu.
It sounds as though he's enjoying dessert.
Hmm?
This kitchen isn't going to scrub itself!
Oh man, this is the worst!
My athlete's foot is gone!
I shall await your return, my new friends.
Molte Crazy.
Unless I'm mistaken, you're Jotaro Kujo.
I'm with the Speedwagon Foundation.
Until you hear otherwise,
any electrical wiring including
phone lines poses a threat
and that's why I've come to
deliver this message in person.
At noon tomorrow I expect to
arrive in the port of Morioh.
Joseph Joestar
Anytime I need to see a
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taken to a place
with a crystal mind.
A magenta feeling, take a
shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to
explain, I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
To the human kind of all
that I need to, I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I got to find you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I got to find you.